Anthony Gentile

123 Carpenter Street, Philadelphia, PA, 12345 antho nygent i le @ examp le.com {123}456-7890

A Pizza Delivery Driver with three years of experience specializing in safe driving, traffic laws, route navigation, and customer service, Possesses a safe driving record and a strong history of navigating traffic and weather conditions without incident.

Education

High School Diploma Benjamin Franklin High School, Philadelphia, PA September 2015 - June 2019

Key Skills

- Safe Driving
- Food Delivery Service
- ♦ Route Navigation
- Customer Service
- ♦ Traffic Laws

Professional Experience

Pizza Delivery Driver

Franko and Luigi's, Philadelphia, PA | May 2020 - Present

- Perform 30-35 food product deliveries per day for an upscale pizzeria in Center City, navigate a wide range of weather and traffic conditions safely, maintain an accident-free record, and ensure on-time delivery for customers
- Utilize Google Maps and Ways to plan optimal routes and circumvent obstacles in the event of road closures caused by construction and traffic accidents
- Communicate with customers to ensure compliance with delivery specifications and maintain strict adherence to Covid-19 safety protocols

Pizza Delivery Driver

Little Caesars, Philadelphia, PA | June 2019 - May 2020

- Managed 20-25 delivery orders daily for a prominent pizza chain, ensured accuracy of orders prior to delivery, and communicated with customers to resolve issues, process payments, and identify solutions to ensure satisfaction
- Ensured safety of company vehicles during periods of high volume and traffic and planned routes effectively to ensure on-time delivery for customers